ilance.com 2017-01-25

# ILance - Privacy Policy | Auction Software Built to Scale.

### **Privacy Policy**

ILance Inc. takes your right to privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable using this web site. This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information (referred to as "data" below) that may be collected by this site. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by ILance Inc., nor does it apply to persons that are not employees or agents of ILance Inc., or that are not under the control of ILance Inc.

### **I. Personally-identifiable information**

This site only collects personally-identifiable information from you if you choose to provide this information to us. Personally-identifiable information collected with your consent may include, for example, name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone number, user id and password (if you have one). Information that you may supply in connection with applying for an account with us, information about orders you place, any responses you choose to provide to survey questions, or any inquires you may make through our Web site.

### **II. Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. This site uses first and third party cookies (session and persistent), however personally identifiable information is not collected through the use of cookies. Cookies are used to determine whether a visitor is unique or whether a visitor has viewed our site before. Cookies are also used in sections of this site which require user log-in to authenticate and validate users and to determine whether a user's session is active or has timed-out.

While most browsers are set to accept cookies by default, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you before accepting them. Your browser manufacturer has information on changing the default setting for your specific browser.

### **III. Nonpersonally-identifiable information**

This site also collects nonpersonally-identifiable information. For example, as you browse this Web site we may collect information about your visit, your country, state and city but not about you personally. Via Web server logs, for example, we may monitor statistics such as: the number of people that visit our site, which page(s) are visited on our site, from which domain our visitors come (e.g., google.com, hotmail.com, etc.), and which browsers people use to visit our site (e.g., Firefox, Chrome, Internet Explorer, etc.). Additionally, our Web site uses tools to help prevent fraud by utilizing a number of Geo-location features to assist us in analyzing this data to better tailor our Web site and overall user experience.

### **ONWARD TRANSFER**

We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to comply with the law or legal process.

### **SECURITY**

Once we receive personally-identifiable information, we take steps to protect its security on our systems. In the event we request or transmit sensitive information, such as credit card information, we use industry standard, secure socket layer ("SSL") encryption and never store credit card information as a strict company policy.

### **POLICY CHANGES**

We may revise this online privacy policy from time to time. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on the Web site. If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via e-mail. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner.

Last updated: July 17, 2013
